JUPITER:
Technically speaking, I'm an alien.
And from the perspective of Immigration,
an illegal one.
My parents met at the university
in Saint Petersburg...
...where he taught Astrophysics...
...and she taught Applied Mathematics.
My mother fell in love with him
when she found him almost frozen to death...
...on the bank of the Neva,
staring at the stars.
[ALEKSA SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Tonight, the sky is completely full of miracles.
JUPITER:
My mother won't talk much...
...about that time.
- But my aunt Nino told me about my father.
ALEKSA: Max...
JUPITER:
His name was...
...Maximilian Jones.
And he was the son of
an English diplomat...
...who always saw the best in people.
[IN RUSSIAN]
JUPITER: I often wonder if what happened
to my mother and father...
...changed me from someone
who might have seen the best...
...in people...
...to someone
who always expects the worst.
How's my Jupiter?
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Not a planet, the planet.
The biggest and most beautiful planet
in our solar system.
She is our Jupiter.
[IN ENGLISH] Over my dead body
we will name her "Jupiter."
Soon you will discover...
...that your mother can be
extraordinarily unreasonable at times.
- Hm.
- But fortunately...
...for us, she remains susceptible
to your father's particular...
- Heh-heh.
- ...charm.
[CHUCKLING]
[MEN YELLING IN RUSSIAN]
ALEKSA [IN RUSSIAN]:
[IN RUSSIAN]
MAXIMILIAN:
No, oh, no!
Not the telescope, please!
Don't take the telescope...
...Please!
[MAXIMILIAN GRUNTS]
[ALEKSA GASPS]
ALEKSA:
Max! Max!
[ALEKSA SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
JUPITER:
In her grief...
...my mother pushed everyone
except her sister out of her life.
[ALEKSA SCREAMING]
Somewhere in the middle of the Atlantic...
...she pushed me out too.
[BABY CRYING]
I was born without a country.
Without a home.
Without a father.
But I was born...
...in the House of Leo...
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
...with Jupiter rising
at 23 degrees ascendant.
According to my aunt...
...this is supposed to mean
that I am destined for great things...
...and that I will find
the one true love of my life.
ALEKSA:
Jupiter?
Coming!
ALEKSA: You finish the bathroom yet?
- Not yet.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
We still have...
- ...another house tonight.
- I'll be fast.
JUPITER:
The problem with astrology?
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Total bullshit.
KALIQUE:
What was the name of this planet?
TITUS:
Zalintyre, I think.
Have you ever seen a harvest?
Oh, no. Never.
But I've heard they feel no pain.
[FLIES BUZZING]
It's all quite humane,
from what I've been told.
TITUS: There are administrators to make sure
everything is done according to code, but still...
...it can be rather...
...affecting.
Now you sound like Mother.
[TITUS SCOFFS]
Most of them were miserable
in their lives...
...and what we do for them is a mercy.
Balem, thank you for responding.
We were just admiring...
...this ledger from your latest success.
Well done, brother.
The House of Abrasax...
...continues to thrive...
...despite the squandering
of your inheritance.
I must say, you're looking
a little worse for wear.
Could it be success
does not agree with you?
And you look so well.
Could it be that failure agrees with you?
You may have inherited Mother's head
for business, but I inherited her heart.
What does that leave me?
Her beauty.
Liar.
Her humor.
Her unluckiness in love?
Her fetish for wrinkles.
BALEM: If this is to be another
of your eulogies, Titus...
...I have more important matters to attend.
It was her birthday recently.
I get sentimental. I was going through
Mother's old sheave-work...
...and I came across a description
of a planet she claimed...
...was the most rare and beautiful estate
she ever owned.
I believe she named it...
Earth.
Earth. It was part of your inheritance,
wasn't it?
I was moved by her description
and I was wondering...
...if there was any chance
you might be willing to part with it.
KALIQUE:
Titus...
...didn't you bother
to look at the sheaves?
That planet is worth more than
all of your estates combined.
Really?
I had no idea.
Kalique.
Balem.
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTS]
Jupiter, get up.
[MOANS]
Get up.
Jupiter. Make the coffee. Come on.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Oh, I hate my life.
ALEKSA [IN RUSSIAN]:
[ALARM CLOCK BEEPING]
Jupiter, hurry up.
That one goes next to...
...that one.
ALEKSA:
Jupiter.
Get the garbage after this.
- Have you finished the bathroom?
- No.
ALEKSA:
Jupiter!
I hate my life.
Damn it.
Told you.
Lycantant.
- Another Hunter.
RAZO: And ex-Legion.
He was a Skyjacker.
How do you know that?
The boots.
There was a Hunter in the Legion.
A legend.
Could track a single gene in the Gyre.
No matter who or what he is...
...he's after our bounty.
That's him.
It's got to be.
We should warn Lord Balem.
That is what we should do...
...but do you trust me?
This matter must be handled with delicacy.
MALIDICTES:
I understand, Lady Kalique.
KALIQUE: Neither Balem nor Titus
must suspect my involvement.
Of course, Your Majesty.
You believe the Hunters can be trusted?
Trust is an illusion, my lady.
I believe only in mutual self-interest.
They want another life. We can offer it.
Make the deal.
NIGHT:
Welcome back, Lord Balem.
It has been too long.
I have not crossed the vastness of space
for your pleasantries, Mr. Night.
Of course, my lord.
We have verified the geneprint.
Most unfortunate news.
I believe Titus is aware of the Recurrence.
My spies whisper, but cannot substantiate.
So you have her print,
but you don't have her?
Mr. Tskalikan?
The Keepers traced the print
to a medical clinic.
They're eliminating every lead.
We have a name. Dunlevy.
Katherine Dunlevy.
Well, I want Miss Dunlevy found...
...and I want her dead.
Black. Classic?
À la mode? À la...
- No.
- Katherine, I'm done.
Jupiter! Help, please?
Wow...
...what's the occasion?
Austin Davis is taking me to dinner.
I think he's gonna ask me to marry him.
Do you wanna marry him?
Jupiter, he's the number eight richest
bachelor under 30 in America.
He speaks fluent Chinese and German.
He was an alternate
on the Olympic curling team.
Solid résumé.
Yeah. I mean, it sounds
totally Cinderella, doesn't it?
Sure.
Then why do I feel like
I'm about to throw up? Oh, God.
I just don't remember Cinderella puking.
I kind of remember her
dancing with a bunch of mice.
Have you ever...
...fallen in love, Jupiter?
You know, my mom says that love
is just a fairy tale for little girls.
That really...
...it's all just urges and obligations.
Wow, that's kind of harsh.
You want my advice?
- Yes.
- If he's really...
...in love with you...
...then he'll understand
that you're just overwhelmed...
...and you need a little time.
- That makes sense.
- Yeah.
What do I wear now?
Something that...
...reminds him of what he is waiting for.
Like that red McQueen...
...or this little Ricci.
[KATHERINE SCREAMS]
Oh, my...
[RINGS]
[GASPS THEN KNOCK ON DOOR]
MAN:
Katherine? Everything all right?
Yeah. No, no, we're good.
I'll be down in a sec.
Picked up a referral. A townhouse.
But it has to be Wednesday.
Wednesday's full. Three houses.
So do four.
[IN RUSSIAN]
- Use English in this house.
ALEKSA [IN ENGLISH]: Use whatever you like.
You sound like Stalin to me.
VASSILY:
Stalin? I'm Stalin?
You don't want the money.
I will give it to, uh, Gleb's crew.
Good.
Thank you.
We'll take it.
- Big surprise.
JUPITER: Cousin, speaking of money...
- ...I was wondering if...
VASSILY: Oh, let me guess.
Another advance.
For what this time? Shoes?
A new phone?
- I'll earn it back.
VASSILY: Ha-ha.
You'll waste it trying to make yourself feel
better buying something you don't need.
So instead of feeling better,
I should save my money and feel worse?
VASSILY:
Exactly.
You are a smart girl, Jupiter.
I admit it's none of my business...
...but that's probably the reason
you are not married.
Men do not like smart women.
Keep talking about my daughter like that...
...I'll ram that latke
so far up your ass...
[IN RUSSIAN]
English.
Hey, hey. hey.
You swore, no fighting at dinner.
Jupiter, what is the money for?
No, you're right.
It's nothing I need.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Hey, what was that about?
Not having second thoughts?
What if I am?
Jupiter...
...these people, they're counting on you.
Have you even looked at this thing?
Why do they have to use words
like "harvesting"? It's just creepy.
Why would you read this?
You heard what the doctor said.
It's not a big deal.
You go in, cash comes out.
This money, I'm telling you,
I have real plans...
...serious plans.
I believe this money's
gonna mean something...
...possibly life-changing for both of us.
Okay.
- Okay.
- You will not regret this.
All right.
I promise.
- I promise.
- All right. Wait, I have a question.
Why do you get 10 grand...
...and I get 5? They're not your eggs.
That's capitalism, babe.
Shit rolls downhill.
Profits flow up.
NURSE 1:
Ms. Dunlevy?
Excuse me.
You are Katherine Dunlevy, aren't you?
The doctor is ready.
JUPITER: I think something's wrong.
- It's the hormones...
- ...dear.
NURSE 2: Don't worry.
You'll be fine.
DOCTOR:
Trust me, honey.
I could do this procedure
with my eyes closed.
JUPITER:
No, no, no! Please. Please, I can't!
Just relax.
JUPITER:
I can't move my arms.
What's happening?
- Stop. What are you doing?
DOCTOR: Get a sample.
Make sure this is the right one.
Wait, stop. Please!
Please, stop!
It's her.
Good. Kill her.
JUPITER:
Please, please!
Stop. Please help me.
Oh, my God!
You all right?
Who are you?
Caine Wise. I'm here to help you.
[MOANING]
[FAMULUS CLEARS THROAT]
[CLEARS THROAT]
FAMULUS:
Pardon me, Lord Titus.
Only good news is allowed in here,
Famulus.
We received an FTL from Mr. Wise.
He says he has the girl.
Brilliant.
Then send the transport immediately.
At once, my lord.
[THUD]
CAINE: Thought it would make you
feel better when you woke up.
- What?
- The gun.
It works better if you flip the switch
by your thumb.
Careful. You've been asleep
for almost 12 hours.
Where am I?
You're still in Chicago.
Okay, good.
- My clothes?
- Um, you were still in...
...the paper clinic gown.
- Uh-uh. Can't really think about that right now.
- Look...
...Jupiter...
...is that your name?
- How do you know?
- I'm sorry.
Just trying to figure out what happened.
You must have used a false name...
...and their tests tripped the Monitor
to your geneprint.
What are you saying?
I mean, yes, I used a false name...
...but lots of people do that in there.
What does that have to do
with what happened?
Okay. When I was in the Legion,
they gave me Protocols for this.
It can be...
...difficult for Terrsies, or people
from underdeveloped worlds...
...to hear that their planet is not
the only inhabited planet in the Verse.
Has to be the anesthesia.
I mean, it's gotta be a dream.
The Protocol actually says that most Terrsies
will say that this has to be a dream.
Yeah, because a dream is the only way
any of this makes sense.
Compared to what?
The idea that
you're the only intelligent species...
...on the only inhabitable planet
in a universe so full of planets...
...you don't have a number
to describe how many there are?
Are you saying you're an alien?
Genomgineered human.
They cut my DNA with the DNA
of something like a wolf. I'm a Lycantant.
Bred for the military...
...but that didn't work out for me.
And those things at the clinic?
Keepers.
They're from the Diorite System,
but they're genetically repurposed...
...to act as Monitors and watchdogs.
And they're trying to kill me?
- Yes.
- Why me?
Please. This has to be a mistake.
These people don't make
those kind of mistakes.
What if I say no? What if I don't
go with you? What if I go home?
What? Are they gonna
come after me again?
TSKALIKAN:
An FTL, my lord.
There was...
...a problem at the clinic.
A former Legionnaire...
...was involved.
A Legionnaire?
What about the girl?
Still alive.
Double our security deployment.
Destroy any ship that comes near the planet.
Go!
Wow.
[JUPITER GASPS]
Are those...
...flying boots?
They use the force of gravity...
...redirecting it into deferential
equation slopes that you can surf.
Yeah. I heard "gravity" and "surf."
Up is hard. Down is easy.
Thank you. Wow.
[WHIRRING]
Our ride's here.
You ready?
Ready?
Ready to walk out of a 100-story window
with you and your gravity boots onto...
This might make it easier.
Oh! Okay.
[JUPITER SCREAMS]
Sorry.
Oh, shit.
- Hold tight!
- Aah!
Hold on.
Whatever you do, don't let go.
No!
I just need to know what in the hell
is going on here.
We might have stumbled into a war
within the Abrasax family.
The Abrasax family?
One of the most powerful dynasties
in the universe.
I don't care who they are.
You can't just blow up a bunch of buildings
and get away with it.
Those buildings will be rebuilt by tonight.
That's impossible.
Take a look.
Holy crap.
But a bunch of...
...people saw what happened.
They can't cover that up.
You have a picture of a Keeper on your phone
you can't remember taking, can you?
They blanked you. Short-term stuff is easy.
They won't get everybody,
but no one believes the ones...
...that slip through the cracks.
- Oh, my God.
Why is this happening to me?
I asked Titus that question
before I took this job.
All he'd tell me is it was personal.
This is ridiculous.
I have never even met...
...this Titus... What's his name?
- Abrasax.
The House of Abrasax has three...
...primary heirs. The oldest is Balem.
He's the one...
...that controls this planet and is...
...the one who wants you dead.
- That's insane.
I am telling you, I am nobody.
Balem Abrasax wouldn't demolish
an entire city for a nobody.
Kill her.
JUPITER:
Oh, my God!
Stop. Wait, wait! Please stop it.
Please stop! Please help me!
BALEM:
Slow.
There you are.
You know, there are moments...
...when I actually miss you.
But no one understands this universe
like you did.
No one understands me...
...like you did.
Mr. Tskalikan?
How is it possible...
...for a single Splice
to destroy an entire...
...fleet of Shadows?
It was a mistake.
BALEM:
A mistake?
They underestimated him.
The next mistake...
...I hold you accountable.
CAINE:
What are you doing?
I want the owner of this car
to know who borrowed it.
We needed a low profile
to get out of the city.
Oh, my God.
You're bleeding.
Don't worry about it.
- It's fine.
- Lucky for you...
...a woman...
...owns this car.
CAINE:
What is that?
Is that a...?
I just... I wanna thank you...
...for saving my life.
I've never been so scared
when I started falling.
Then you were there and...
Do you do this sort of thing a lot?
No.
Then why did Titus hire you?
Titus hired me because
I'm good at finding people.
Are you taking me to him now?
No.
JUPITER:
How do you know this guy?
A long time ago, he was a friend.
What is he doing living way out here?
He's a Marshall for the Aegis.
The Aegis?
They're like cops.
Space cops. Sure.
[BEES BUZZING]
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
CAINE:
Stinger.
Back from the goddamn dead.
It's kind of funny, both of us
ending up on this planet.
"Funny" ain't the word I'd use.
[GASPS]
[CAINE GRUNTS]
How'd you get out'?
Titus Abrasax.
He hired me to lift her.
Since Deadland ain't taught you
a damn thing...
Just as I was getting used to this life...
...you come back reminding me
what I flushed down the shitter for you.
[CAINE COUGHS]
Where's Kiza?
She used to at least listen...
- ...to my side.
- You stay away from my daughter.
Don't drag me into your male mating...
...rituals.
Hi. I'm Kiza.
Hi.
Jupiter. Nice to meet you.
You used to have...
...mettle in you.
I guess I'm getting a little old.
Old? Look at me. Not a recode
or a drop of Juice in years.
You are a lot uglier...
...than I remember.
Hey!
What is going on here?
[LAUGHS]
Your Majesty.
Uh, thank you.
I'll go to town to pick up
some groceries for dinner.
[KIZA COUGHS]
- I'll go.
- I'm fine, Dad.
Okay. All right.
Let's have a look at you.
It's not pretty, is it?
Clipped and stripped.
The mark of a court-martialed Skyjacker.
You haven't answered my question.
Do you want your wings back...
...or not?
Wait, you had wings?
The best bio-neural-synaptic prosthetic
the military could buy.
Oh, my God. That's amazing.
Your Majesty has no idea of the scientific
miracles that human beings are capable of.
Why won't those human beings
share things...
...like this?
Sharing has never been the strong suit
of your species, Your Majesty.
JUPITER:
Okay...
...what is with this "Your Majesty" thing?
You've never been stung by a bee,
have you?
No.
You know, bees are genetically designed
to recognize royalty.
Royalty?
JUPITER:
Wow.
You are in for a surprise
when you find out what I do for a living.
It's not what you do...
...it's what you are.
They sense it.
Bees aren't like humans.
They don't question or doubt.
Bees don't lie.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
JUPITER:
Oh, I...
Sorry, I gotta take this.
I'm guessing Titus
didn't say anything about it.
- No. Must have slipped his mind.
STINGER: Not easy to picture...
...you making a deal with a Royal.
Titus told me you were posted to this planet,
and said if I helped him...
...he'd get you your wings back,
full Reinstatement.
I figured I owed you.
Yeah, you do.
But if she is a Recurrence...
...then this is a hell of a lot
more important than wings.
VLADIE [OVER PHONE]:
It's life-changing, Jupiter.
Wait till you see this thing.
Two million pixels of resolution.
It's everything I ever wanted.
[VLADIE LAUGHS]
That's great.
Um, is Mom there?
No, she went out with Nino.
They were a little freaked out
when you didn't come home.
I covered, I think it's fine.
How about a little gratitude for your cousin?
This was a cakewalk, right?
Just like I said,
easiest money we ever made. Chi-ching!
It didn't happen.
Ha. "It didn't happen."
- What?
- No, I know. I'm so sorry.
- Oh, no.
- I'm really, really sorry.
- Why?
- There was an accident at the clinic.
Someone got hurt.
Shit! I knew it!
Oh, my God, I knew it.
I can't catch a break.
I cannot catch a single break!
Look, I'm with some people.
- I don't wanna be rude.
- We have to reschedule.
Totally. Tell Mom I'm okay...
- ...and I will call her when I can.
- Wait! Jupe, Jupe?
I already spent the money.
You're in trouble.
Don't touch my stuff!
Balem ordered a blockade.
Nothing is getting on or off this planet.
Aegis Command said
once her geneprint...
...is verified, they'll get an injunction
to take us to Orous.
- So we wait.
- They're sending a Cruiser.
- When?
- Should be here tomorrow.
We won't last the night.
We need a plan.
We need firepower.
If she's what you say she is...
...we won't get off this planet
without a fight.
Stash is in the back.
Is he mad at me?
When he's mad, you'll know it.
He just...
...seems different since we got here.
Caine is...
...complicated.
He's a Lycantant without a pack.
Had the bad luck...
...to be born half-albino.
Runt of the litter.
The Splicer that bred him had to sell him
to the Legion for a loss.
But a Lycantant needs a pack.
It's their center of gravity.
Alone...
...usually they waste away and die...
...unless they become like him.
Fearless.
Relentless.
Perfect hunting machines.
Caine was the best soldier
I ever went into battle with.
Why did he get court-martialed?
I'm sorry.
It's none of my business.
He attacked someone.
He attacked an Entitled.
He bit him.
He bit him?
Tore his throat out.
There's something about the Royals
for Caine. It's instinctual.
They tried to put him down,
but he was...
...under my command so I took the blame.
Two scars across my back as a reward.
JUPITER: You both have marks
on your neck, but they're...
...slightly different.
The brand of the Splicer.
Marcellian Cahun was her name.
She loved bees.
Wow.
My father would be freaking out right now.
Do you know...
...what this will do to people
when they find out the truth?
I don't think that most people
would want to know the truth.
I do.
Okay.
So you've been taught that the birthplace
of the human race is Earth...
...but it's not.
It's actually a planet
in the Cunabulum System...
...called Orous...
...a little over a billion
of your years ago.
Your planet was discovered during what is
commonly called The Great Expansion.
Ah.
At the time...
...Earth was inhabited
by a branch-species of Saurisapian...
...a dangerous human predator
called a Sargorn.
Obviously before any colonization
or resource development...
...could be done safely to your planet...
...a large-scale extinction event
was manufactured...
Damn budget cuts.
Are you talking about dinosaurs?
Mm-hm.
Wait, are you saying your people
killed the dinosaurs?
Technically, they're your people, Majesty.
Come on.
According to Commonwealth records...
...this planet was seeded
by Abrasax Industries...
...roughly 100,000 years ago.
Human DNA
spliced with indigenous species...
...to evolve a fertile population.
That's where the why gets ugly.
Basically...
...the goal is to grow a population
as large as possible.
Once the population exceeds...
...the planet's ability to sustain it...
...it's considered ripe for harvest.
Harvest?
What's going on?
What's wrong with them?
They're here.
- Go.
- Come on.
Caine.
Wait, Caine!
Caine!
Beeswax.
FALQUE:
Gotcha.
[BEES BUZZING]
[YELLING]
Mr. Night...
...I want this facility
running at capacity.
I want full diagnostics
and cost projections...
...for an early harvest.
NIGHT:
Of course, my lord.
What kind of grade
are we getting from the Skim?
Excellent product, sire.
Premium grade.
It's a, um, particularly robust stock.
Assuming market stability,
if we harvest later this century...
...profit margins should eclipse...
...your nearest competitor.
BALEM:
Understand this, Mr. Night.
I will harvest that planet tomorrow...
...before I let her take it from me.
Here we go.
I trust you.
MALIDICTES:
Premium...
...Abrasax, as requested.
Now...
...where is Her Majesty?
[JUPITER GASPS]
SENDI [OVER SPEAKER]:
Good evening, Your Majesty.
Allow me to assist.
- Oh.
- I am Sendi...
- ... your Chamber Presence.
- New clothes?
We wish only to attend...
...your needs.
Where am I?
This is the alcazar of Kalique Abrasax...
...Second Primary of the House of Abrasax.
What's an alcazar?
A fancy way of saying my home.
I'm Kalique.
Jupiter Jones.
I'm sorry...
...for staring, but it's quite astonishing.
What is?
It will be easier to show you.
Could this get any weirder?
KALIQUE:
Imagine it for me.
Meeting your mother
long after she's passed away.
But I'm not your mother.
Your planet is just now
entering its Genetic Age.
You understand very little about something
which is a vital part of our reality.
In our world...
...genes have an almost
spiritual significance.
They are the seeds of our immortality.
When the exact...
...same genes reappear...
...in the exact same order...
...it is for us what you
would call reincarnation.
But how could I be a reincarnation of your
mother unless your mother was from Earth?
My mother was born
before your first cities were built.
Are you some kind of vampire race?
KALIQUE: We are the cause
of a lot of those myths, but I promise...
...my mother was just as human as you or I.
The difference between us
is our knowledge and technology.
How old do you think...
...I am?
- Um...
Late forties?
I recently celebrated my 14th millennium.
You're 14,000 years old?
Fourteen thousand and four, to be precise.
My mother was approaching
her 91st millennium when she passed.
You'd be just as amazed
how quickly it goes.
JUPITER:
If your lives are so long...
...could I ask
how your mother actually died?
She was murdered.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
- Did they ever find out who did it?
- No.
My mother and I did not always get along.
I hope this Recurrence might mean
a second chance for both of us.
Come.
Let me introduce you
to the possibilities of your new life.
[SNIFFS]
Holy crap.
KALIQUE:
Each of us has...
...a code for our optimal
physical condition.
The problem is...
...our genes have an expiration date
which is transferred to our cells.
A long time ago, someone figured out...
...how to replace deteriorating cells
with new ones.
Today, it's as easy as
changing a light bulb.
Where do you get these light bulbs?
You grow them.
Like clones?
No.
Clones lack genetic plasticity.
Several million years ago,
a gene plague caused by cloning...
...nearly annihilated
the entire human race.
I was told that the House of Abrasax
seeded the Earth.
Is that where you get it?
Your Earth is a very small part
of a very large industry.
Feel my skin.
Wow.
In your world, people are used to
fighting for resources...
...like oil, or minerals, or land.
But when you have access
to the vastness of space...
...you realize there's only one resource
worth fighting over...
...even killing for:
More time.
Time is the single most
precious commodity...
...in the universe.
DROID:
Unidentified Lycantant.
Unidentified...
...Lycantant.
Sorry, I just don't understand what you mean
when you say "claim your Title."
It's common for people
in the First Estate...
...to leave a trust
for any potential Recurrence.
My mother wrote her future
self into her will.
Right now, Balem owns the Title to Earth...
...but once you claim it,
the Earth will belong to you.
How can one person own the Earth?
It's just a planet, Jupiter.
In this world, people own things
far more valuable.
You cannot know what it will be like...
...when you're offered
wealth beyond your imagining.
When you can choose
to remain young and beautiful...
...or when you can have the power to change
the lives of your family for the better.
And all you have to do is close your eyes.
JUPITER:
Caine.
This must be the Hunter Titus hired.
- Well-made, by the look of him.
JUPITER: Whoa!
No, no, no. Hey, hey!
It's okay.
- She's on our side.
CAINE: Abrasax...
...don't know any side but their own.
Precisely. And since...
...Jupiter is an Abrasax,
you understand why...
...I helped her get off that planet.
- He contacted the Aegis.
They are entering...
...orbit now.
Excellent.
I had planned to take you myself...
...but the Aegis will insist...
...they handle things from here.
I wish for you
the life you've always dreamed of.
TSING:
Welcome aboard, Your Majesty. My name...
...is Diomika Tsing, captain of this...
...Aegis Cruiser.
- Please call me Jupe.
STINGER: Your Majesty.
Stinger.
- You're all right. Oh.
- For the time being...
...Your Majesty. For the time being.
TSING:
We'll escort you...
...to the Commonwealth Ministry. Anything we
can do to make the journey easier, let us know.
Actually, I'm feeling a little overdressed.
If you maybe have something
I can change into.
By myself.
While I'm awake.
What?
TSKALIKAN:
No! No!
Lord Balem!
It was the Hunters!
They betrayed you in the name...
...of your sister!
Please! Mercy, my lord!
Mercy!
Mr. Greeghan.
Bring her to me.
Yes, my lord.
[DOOR CHIMES]
Come in.
I don't really... Oh, I don't really know
how to work this thing. Oh.
Hi. Come in.
Your Majesty might want to take these.
Portaling can be a little rough
on the royal bowels.
Well, my bowels are anything but royal.
Heh-heh-heh.
Thank you.
You heard the lady down there.
You're an Abrasax now.
No, no...
...I'm a Jones.
Well, except when I'm mad.
- Then I'm a Bolotnikov.
- If that's all you were, you would not be...
...on an Aegis Cruiser
headed to the Hall of Titles.
Yeah, um...
Stinger said that you attacked
an Entitled once.
- Stinger talks too much.
- Is it true?
Does it matter?
Sorry, I get it's none of my business.
I was just trying to understand.
Truth is, I don't know why I did it.
I don't even remember doing it.
It just happened.
We all do things we can't explain.
They said it was...
...in my genes.
- A defect of my genomgineering.
- Hm.
Could explain a lot of things about me.
Like the fact that I have
an uncanny ability...
...to fall for men that don't fall for me.
It's like my internal
compass needle points...
...straight at Mr. Wrong.
Maybe it's my genes.
Maybe I have defective engineering too.
And if that's the case...
...is there any way to fix it?
You are royalty now.
I'm a Splice. You don't...
...understand what that means...
...but I have more in common with a dog
than I have with you.
I love dogs.
I've always loved dogs.
- I should go, Your Majesty.
- Right.
Strap in...
- ...before we portal.
- Right, okay.
"I love dogs"?
Huh.
[GROANS]
PERCADIUM: Welcome, Your Majesty,
to the overpopulated, oozing cesspool...
...we humbly call home.
I did three tours in Abukesh, a battle
that cost the lives of 2 million soldiers.
Rather be back there than have to deal...
...with these bureaucrats.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I am Intergalactic Advocate Bob...
...here to assist you
through the Ascension Process.
Sheave.
This is the authentic Recurrence...
...of Her Ladyship...
...the Abrasax Sovereign...
...and we have come to claim her Title.
You need to file an Inheritance Petition.
If the Title is held, you'll need...
...a transfer of Title.
Thank you.
File a Quit Claim through Central Services,
Section 918.
Next.
You need a Title Survey...
...and geneprint identification
from Wills and Trusts.
I can't touch this without a Tax Number...
...from the Revenue Review.
This is Revenue Request,
not Revenue Review.
[IN SMEGESE]
We can't get the Title without the Tax ID.
[IN ENGLISH]
It goes without saying that...
...graft is incompatible
with my programming.
I think you dropped something.
BUREAUCRAT [IN ENGLISH]:
Press your thumb in the depression.
Seals and Signets...
...are on Sub-33.
Your Majesty.
[MINISTER CLEARS THROAT]
[MINISTER MUTTERING]
Well, well, well.
This is what I have to deal with.
Yeah, yeah. Good.
[COUGHS]
[PANTING]
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
[WHIRRING]
Yeah, very nice.
Would Your Majesty kindly...
...place your wrist here?
Uh, yes.
Palm up, please.
JUPITER:
Sorry.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh! Heh.
MINISTER:
Very good.
Yes.
It's cool.
Very nice. Very nice indeed.
Now, here is your...
...Code and...
...Conduct Guide...
...and your Royal Ways
and Means Commission.
And file this with...
...a Legion Administrator
for your Royal Guard appointment. Yes?
Okay.
Well, congratulations, Your Majesty...
...and my deepest condolences.
Thank you?
[LAUGHS]
I will never complain about the DMV...
...ever again.
Well, you did it. It's official.
You are now Entitled.
Entitled to what? Like...
...free parking? Key to the city?
I mean...
...what does it even really mean?
It means Your Majesty's life
is gonna change...
...if she wants it to.
Can you say that again?
Just the "Your Majesty" part.
Your Majesty.
That's interesting.
When other people say it,
it makes me...
...really uncomfortable.
But when you say it...
I don't know.
There are things about my life
I would like to change...
...but it doesn't make
me a different person.
It doesn't change the things that
matter to me or who I care about.
I'm still the same me.
If Your Majesty says so.
Well, you're the one
with the Entitled instinct.
Is there something happening to you
right now?
Does any part of you wanna bite me?
No.
Well, maybe.
Go ahead.
How can Your Majesty be so sure...
...if, as you've said...
...your compass is broken?
Tell me that I'm wrong.
You used to work for Titus,
but that's not true anymore.
So why stick around?
Why help me?
Because of Stinger.
He thinks if we help you, then...
...you might help us get
back in the Legion.
- I see.
STINGER: Good to know...
...we're both liars.
What is this?
I'm sorry.
FAMULUS:
Hello, Mr. Wise.
Don't make this harder than it has to be.
I'm sorry, man.
TITUS:
Welcome, Your Majesty.
I am Titus Abrasax...
...Third Primary of the House of Abrasax...
...and it is my profound...
...honor...
...to meet you.
You are aware that
by detaining me without consent...
...you are in direct
violation of Statute 27b/6.
Your Highness is a quick study
of the Entitled Code, I see.
I also know that I can file
a tax grievance against you...
...unless you take me
where I want to go.
I'd be delighted to take you
wherever you'd like.
I'd like to go home.
Very well.
Set a course for Earth.
At once, my lord.
In the meantime,
since you've invoked Code and Conduct...
...I trust you'll do me the honor
of dining with me.
Very well.
The Aegis is involved now...
...more than likely tracking you
as we speak.
We've committed no crime.
How about detaining a Royal?
Her Majesty is hardly detained.
Where is she?
Dining with Lord Titus, of course.
Unless they've moved on to dessert.
Your Highness looks ravishing.
What have you done with Caine?
I know you do not trust me right now,
but I promise I am not your enemy.
[JUPITER SCOFFS]
Please.
Mr. Wise and I had an arrangement.
He broke our contract. For that, I promised
to return him to the Deadland.
Is that open to negotiation?
Everything is open to negotiation.
I confess I feel I have you
at somewhat of a disadvantage.
Because you kidnapped me?
From the moment I saw your geneprint,
I knew so many things about you...
...because I was very close to my mother.
So close, in fact...
...that I could tell by the way
she raised her eyebrows...
...exactly what she was thinking.
At this point, I probably know more
about you than you know yourself.
Shoot.
Just like her.
Always expecting the worst from people.
Funny how often people
exceed those expectations.
That distrust in others,
in the world and even in yourself...
...has made it difficult
for you to fall in love.
Until now.
You're in love with Mr. Wise, aren't you?
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but this isn't love.
All Mr. Wise wants from me
is to make him a Legionnaire.
Mother was also a terrible liar.
Your sister told me you would do
anything in your power...
...to prevent me from claiming my Title.
What makes you think Kalique
told the truth?
- Why would she lie?
- Kalique is...
...in competition with Balem.
The loss of Earth will impact his position...
...in the market. His loss is her gain.
Same can be said for you.
Not long ago, yes.
- I would have been just like them.
- And now?
I knew this moment would come
when your geneprint was first confirmed.
When it did, I was going to...
...ask you one question...
...and if you gave me the right answer,
I was going to change my life...
...irrevocably.
Come with me.
[JUPITER GASPS]
JUPITER:
What is that?
It has many names:
ReGenX, ReCell, Nectar.
There are various levels
of usefulness and quality, but this...
...is the most pure and most valuable
solution made by the House of Abrasax.
Kalique came out of a bath...
Naturally, my sister didn't
explain what it is...
...or where it comes from.
It comes from people.
Each unit is refined from approximately
a hundred human beings.
What?
Your planet is a farm...
...Jupiter. There are thousands
of planets like yours...
...set up by families like mine
to supply...
...an ever increasing demand
for more time.
Are you saying you killed
a hundred people to make this?
Not me, but...
...yes, someone did.
Not unlike...
...butchering a herd of cattle.
[JUPITER GASPS]
- Oh, my God.
- It's all right.
It's all right.
My mother went through a change
at the end of her life.
She felt exactly as you do now.
But when she tried...
...to do something to stop this business,
she was murdered.
I believe the same thing
is about to happen to me...
...because I began to carry out
the work she started.
That is why I hired Mr. Wise to find you.
I needed someone I could trust.
I cannot allow...
...my brother or sister
to end up with control...
...over my part of the Abrasax inheritance.
I want to know that when I die...
...you will be my heir.
Which brings us at last to my question.
Jupiter Jones...
[GASPS]
...will you marry me?
Pleasure doing business with you.
I told your men not to take Caine.
You should have left him on Orous.
Unfortunately, my lord promised Mr. Wise...
...that if he betrayed us,
he'd be fed to the Void.
Titus Abrasax...
...is a man of his word.
So was I.
GEMMA:
We got the trace.
Outside the Cleopeides.
Better get a move on.
Don't sound like Caine's got a lot of time.
Put him back in the brig.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Lord Titus will see you now.
You should have told me
the truth about why...
...you wanted her.
What good would that have done?
If I did...
...Jupiter would be dead...
...and Balem would still own the Earth.
Lies are a necessity.
They are the source of meaning...
...of belief and hope.
Honestly, lies are sometimes...
...the only reason I get out of bed.
I'm particularly fond
of the lies we tell ourselves.
Like the lie you are now concocting...
...that somehow you'll survive
being tossed into the Void...
...and find some way to rescue Miss Jones.
You can't kill her.
The Title will just remain with her family.
Well, not once Her Majesty and I
are married.
EMERGENCY GUIDE [OVER SPEAKER]:
Emergency pressurization complete.
You have 37 minutes of air remaining.
Please get to an airlock or life pod
immediately.
ALEKSA:
You did what?
- Shame on you.
- Wait.
You're telling me you...
...convinced your cousin to sell her eggs?
Yeah?
What do you think she is...
...a goddamn chicken?
- Dad! She wanted to!
IRINA: Enough!
She wanted to do it.
It wasn't all my plan.
- You little shit, Vladie!
VLADIE: She begged me.
She wanted to buy some stupid telescope.
- Deal wasn't good for me.
- Telescope?
It's a curse.
Our family is cursed.
VASSILY:
I don't care what she wanted!
You don't...
...treat your cousin...
...like chicken!
[RUMBLING]
[SCREAMING]
VLADIE:
Dad!
GREEGHAN:
You're the mother.
Be gentle with this one.
EMERGENCY GUIDE [OVER SPEAKER]:
You have zero minutes of air remaining.
Carbon dioxide levels at maximum.
Please get to an airlock or life pod
immediately.
You have zero minutes of air remaining.
Is he alive?
- Few ticks later and he wouldn't be.
- He's gonna kill her.
He's gonna kill her.
Is there a problem?
- No, I'm so sorry, I don't think I can do this.
TITUS: I told you not to think about it...
...like a wedding on your world.
It's just a contract...
...in order to protect people.
Innocent people.
- I get that...
TITUS: Wish I could show you the four planets...
...I inherited.
Nothing as large as your Earth...
...but each unique and beautiful
in its own way.
I'd love to see them one day, but...
Right now, I need to speak to Caine.
I see.
You still don't trust me,
even though you trust the man I hired.
I'm sorry...
...but talking to Mr. Wise
is no longer possible.
Why?
He attacked a Servitant
and destroyed a host of guards.
Given his history, I was advised
to return him to the authorities.
You do know what he did, don't you?
And you still trust him.
Beauty and her Beast.
Why wouldn't you tell me sooner?
[TITUS SIGHS]
So you can plead...
...for this.
The original Rite of Pardon and
Reinstatement my law has procured...
...for him and Mr. Apini.
I kept it, knowing how you felt,
even if you wouldn't admit it.
To be fair, there was a time when I would
have used something like this against you.
But now, if you can believe anything,
Jupiter...
...the life of one Splice
matters very little to me...
...compared to the lives of my subjects.
Goodbye, Miss Jones.
Titus.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
- Oh-oh.
- I need your help.
Sure you want to go into a fight
with someone you can't trust?
Has anyone in your crew ever
broke through a field of Warhammers?
What happened?
Kiza's got the Bug.
Couldn't afford the ReCode.
I love...
...my daughter, Caine.
She's the only good thing
I've done with this life.
You would have done the same.
- Any other family issues I should know about?
- No.
Loans?
Money problems?
Uh, no.
He's good. Let's go.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Holy crap.
PERCADIUM:
Portal at mass.
Nine ticks to intercept.
[GASPS]
Abrasax Clipper D-Gamma-9,
this is the Aegis.
Cut your engines...
...and prepare to be boarded.
The Aegis are demanding to board, sire.
Do what you must,
but keep them off this ship.
SHIP VOICE [OVER SPEAKER]:
- is at full stage.
Warhammers are launching.
Here we go.
TITUS:
Your Highness.
Who are all these people?
Just Sims.
A necessary feature for all royal weddings.
As I told you, these are matters of State,
not of the heart.
Shall we begin?
Let's hit it!
I, Titus Abrasax...
...take Jupiter Jones to be my wife.
I enter into this union...
...being of sound mind
and of my own volition.
MINISTER:
Would my liege...
...place his hand here...
...to receive the Signifying Bond?
CAINE:
Break left, I'm going right!
Aah! I'm hit!
[CROWD MURMURING]
Your turn.
Where are you at, Stinger?
- I've lost a wing plate!
CAINE [OVER COMM]: I got you!
Roll, roll, roll!
Aah!
I, Jupiter Jones...
...take Titus Abrasax to be my husband.
I enter into this union being...
I enter into this union...
...being of sound mind...
...and of my own volition.
We're clear!
Would Your Majesty place her hand here...
...to receive the Signifying Bond?
I'm tracking heavy Sim activity.
That's gotta be where she is.
Cover me!
What's going on?
What was that?
No!
Caine?
Whoa!
Mr. Wise, you are as resourceful
as promised.
This whole thing was nothing but a lie.
Was the ring executed?
JUPITER:
No.
CAINE:
Once you were married...
...he was going to murder you.
He told me right before
he threw me out the airlock.
[SIGHS]
Honestly...
...I don't believe my mother was ever...
...as beautiful...
...or as gullible as you, my dear.
May I kill him?
Just get me out of here.
[DOOR OPENS]
CAINE: Your Majesty?
- Don't call me that.
Titus will pay. Captain Tsing...
- ...has already filed...
- I don't care.
The more you care...
...the more the world
finds ways to hurt you for it.
That's your pardon.
Congratulations...
...you and Stinger
are officially Skyjackers again.
Thank you.
- When we were in the Commonwealth...
- I don't wanna talk.
I really just wanna go home.
Mom?
Oh, God, no. Nino!
Good evening...
...Your Majesty.
Easy, dingo.
Where's my family?
NIGHT:
Well, we can all only hope...
...that they remain unharmed. Heh.
I see you have the standard-issue
Abrasax temper.
A transfer of Title
has already been processed.
You and your lord
are trespassing in this precinct.
We are aware of all current legalities.
I have been instructed...
...to offer Your Grace a proposal.
What proposal?
NIGHT: You are to come with me
to meet my lord. There you will...
...abdicate your Title...
...and in return, my lord guarantees...
...that he will do
everything in his power...
...to see that no harm
comes to you or your family.
You can't do it.
You cannot trust these people.
If you abdicate, you'll have nothing
to protect yourself.
[CHUCKLES]
You'll kill them if I don't come with you.
NIGHT:
Your Majesty...
...I could not even consider
such an abhorrent crime.
He's lying.
You wound me, Mr. Wise.
CAINE:
If I were trying to wound you...
...you wouldn't be breathing.
GREEGHAN:
If it makes everyone feel warm and cozy...
...the Aegis is welcome to follow us.
No.
She won't go anywhere with you.
Very well.
I will inform my lord
you have rejected his offer.
Wait.
This is my family.
It's too dangerous.
I know...
...but it's not your decision.
This is Greeghan, on approach.
We have an escort.
Mr. Nesh, keep us close.
Mr. Wise, that pacing is not helping.
CONTROLLER [OVER COMM]:
The gate is prepped and standing by, sir.
Captain Tsing.
They're closing the vortex. Shields up.
Accelerate to full.
We've lost all nav-com!
Grav-drive not responding.
Shields failing!
Get us out of here!
SHIP VOICE [OVER SPEAKER]:
Frozen ionization ratio critical.
Damn it.
JUPITER:
Where's my family?
You should have stayed dead.
I am not your mother.
No, my mother...
...never cleaned a toilet in her life.
Maybe that was her problem.
[BALEM CHUCKLES]
My mother.
My mother...
...taught me what was necessary...
...to rule in this universe.
Like killing people?
I create life!
And I destroy it.
Life is an act of consumption...
...Jupiter.
To live...
...is to consume.
Now, the human beings on your planet...
...are merely a resource waiting to...
...be converted into capital.
And this entire enterprise...
...is just a small part in a vast...
...and beautiful machine defined...
...by evolution...
...designed to a single purpose:
To create profit.
If that's what your mother taught you,
then I can see why you hated her.
I loved my mother.
And yet, you're trying to kill me.
My mother...
...made me understand...
...that every human society...
...is a pyramid and that some lives...
...will always matter more than others.
It is better to accept this...
...than to pretend it isn't true.
Is that why you killed her?
How dare you?
STINGER:
I know because of...
...who and what you are,
you're unable to say this...
...so I'll say it for you.
You lied in the Commonwealth
because you're a Hunter...
...who's been searching
for one thing his whole life.
You survived so long without it...
...the fact that you may have found it
terrifies you...
...but not as much as the fact
that she's down there...
...buried in several tons of hurricane.
And if you want to see her again...
...then you take my advice:
You get down there and you start digging.
This is a Notice of Abdication.
You will confess your genetic incapacity
to rule...
...and you will return...
...the Title to its natural heir.
Where's my family?
Mom.
Oh, God.
I will do...
...whatever it is that you want
so long as the Aegis...
...can get my family out safely.
You are in no position to negotiate.
JUPITER:
Stop.
Stop, stop!
I will do anything.
Please, you win. I beg...
...of you, stop.
Please.
TSING [OVER COMM]:
Mr. Wise, as a matter of public record...
...I strongly advise against this reckless
course of action that will almost certainly...
...cost you your life.
Understood.
Off the record, I will tell you
that you're a man of rare courage...
...and I pray your aim is true.
Thank you.
Aah!
And hereby return the Title...
...to its original heir, Balem Abrasax.
Once I seal this...
...how long until you harvest the Earth?
I can promise that you will not see it.
But how long?
You knew nothing of harvesting before.
Why should it matter now?
Remember...
...why you're here.
I came here to try to protect my family.
Seal that sheave...
...and you and your family...
...will return home safely.
If I don't seal this...
...you can't touch the Earth,
even if you kill me.
Is that right?
That planet belongs to me.
It is my right.
Not anymore.
You have no idea what you are doing.
I am making sure that whatever you do
to me and my family...
...you're not able to do to anyone else's.
This is not a game.
I am not my brother or my sister.
If you do not seal...
Beg pardon, my lord.
- Mr. Night.
NIGHT: It is an emergency.
The grav-hull is ruptured.
The gas is reacting to the stockworks.
You seal it now.
Seal it now!
JUPITER: Unh!
NIGHT: My lord...
...is that advisable...
...without the Abdication?
BALEM:
Kill her!
Here, take this.
- Get your family out.
JUPITER: Wait.
In case we don't get the chance again.
Go.
GEMMA:
I'm getting readings...
...from the refinery. It's destabilized.
Sinking fast.
PERCADIUM:
Captain, the gate's open.
It's an evacuation.
Get us down there, Nesh.
- Aah!
BALEM: You're just like her.
You won't pull that trigger.
Aah!
Jupiter!
You hurt me.
And I'm gonna make you...
...regret it.
- Captain, I'm tracking a ping.
- Is it Her Majesty?
GEMMA:
Signature unknown.
Attempting to lock in.
This is Captain Tsing of the Aegis.
We are tracking. Can you click back?
CAINE [OVER COMM]:
This is Caine.
Yes.
CAINE:
I have the family.
Can you extract?
MEDIC 1: Get them strapped into stasis.
MEDIC 2: This one's dehydrated.
MEDIC 3: Get me a full tox on this one.
- Caine, we can't wait long.
Give me every second you can.
Is this familiar, Mother?
Does some part of you remember this
like I do?
Well, this is how...
...it began.
We were fighting.
Do you remember what you said?
Get back!
I remember what you said.
You told me you hated your life.
It's the truth.
And you begged me to do it.
You begged me to do it!
I am not your damn mother.
Jupiter.
Just breathe. You're all right.
Just breathe.
My family?
They're safe.
Medic!
We can't hold much longer.
Set a portal.
Now.
I don't need to tell you how dangerous...
Then don't!
I promised every second I could.
Oh, no.
Twelve ticks to portal.
Eruption imminent!
PERCADIUM:
Portal's open!
Come on, Caine.
Core-gen's about to blow!
Now!
Everyone all right?
ALL:
Aye, captain.
GEMMA:
Captain...
...I don't understand,
but I'm pinging Mr. Wise again.
What?
CAINE [OVER COMM]:
Hello in there.
Wise, where are you?
CAINE:
Why don't you take
a look out your window?
You might want to open the door for us
or something.
[ALL CHEERING]
[ALARM CLOCK BEEPING]
ALEKSA:
Jupiter.
Jupiter, get up. Make the coffee.
Morning, Nino.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Morning, Mama.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Jupiter.
JUPITER:
Yeah?
- Need help?
- All done.
[VASSILY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
VASSILY:
English, please.
Vladie.
Look, Jupiter...
...I know we don't always see eye to eye.
[SCOFFS]
But, um...
- ...well...
- For you, my dear.
- Why? It's not even my birthday.
- Vladie told us what you wanted...
- ...the money for.
- You didn't.
No.
Are you serious?
Oh, my God.
We all pitched in.
Thank you.
Your father was good man...
...and I loved him very much.
And you should have this.
Could we take it to the roof?
Um...
I'm so sorry. I...
I actually have a date.
What?
- What?
- Is he Russian?
IRINA: Is he rich?
MIKKA: Does he have a brother?
Does he need a big television?
How is he with a mop?
What's his name?
- What's his sign?
JUPITER: I don't know.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I guess you can say
my family's complicated...
...the way that most families are.
- You think you'll ever tell them?
- What?
- That I own the Earth?
- Mm-hm.
Heh. Are you kidding me?
They'd have me locked up.
And I wouldn't blame them either.
Besides...
...I'm still trying to understand
exactly what it means myself.
Maybe it means Your Majesty's
planet has a different future...
...than the one that was planned for it.
Say that again.
- You mean "Your Majesty"?
- Mm.
That really works for me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
All right.
Come on.
That ain't bad either.
[GASPS]
Well, I can get used to this.
You ready?
Watch this.
Ha-ha!
Whoo! Ha-ha-ha!
[JUPITER LAUGHING]
Whee!
Whoo!
[JUPITER LAUGHS]
Whee!